hwdrivers.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy policy | HWDrivers.com

**Please review this document carefully before using or accessing HWDrivers.com. By using or accessing HWDrivers.com you agree to be legally bound by the terms and conditions set forth below. If you do not want to be bound by the terms and conditions listed below you may not use or access HWDrivers.com and should stop such use immediately.**

**HWDrivers.com shall have the right at any time to remove or add any terms or conditions of this Agreement without notice or liability to you. Any changes to this Agreement shall be effective immediately after the posting of such changes on HWDrivers.com. You agree to review this Agreement from time to time and agree that any subsequent use by you of this website following changes to this Agreement constitutes your acceptance of all such changes. If any provision of this Agreement is declared invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions of this Agreement will remain in effect. The user agrees to comply with all applicable laws in using our service.**

  1. **What information do we collect?**  
We do not collect any information. All users visit our site anonymously. 
  2. **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information ([learn more](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie "HTTP cookie")). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 
  3. **Third party ads**  
We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out). 
  4. **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 
  5. **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 
  6. **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 
  7. **Transmission of data over the Internet**  
There are inherent dangers in the use of any software available for download on the Internet, and HWDrivers.com cautions you to make sure that you completely understand the potential risks before downloading any of the software. You are solely responsible for adequate protection and backup of the data and equipment used in connection with any of the software, and HWDrivers.com will not be liable for any damages that you may suffer in connection with using, modifying or distributing any of the software. 
  8. **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 
  9. **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 
  10. **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 
  11. **Agreement**  
Please also visit our Agreement section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Agreement page. 

We've updated our privacy policy, effective May 25, 2018. Learn More

The website uses cookies for analytics, personalized content and ads. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to this use. Read More

Got it
